In this video, I am going to tell you that if
you do insurance for a two-wheeler, four-wheeler or any other big vehicle,
your
insurance is complete and you have
also received the hard copy of your insurance,
but your insurance has
not been updated online. Your insurance is
not showing online on the net. So, what will you do
now? What process do you have to follow? I am going to
tell you in this video,
friends. First of all, I will
open it in the files manager and show it to you.
I have an insurance copy and
this insurance is complete
but this insurance is not showing on the net yet. So,
here you can see,
this is the PF Shakeel here. As soon as I
click on it,
something like this five-page insurance
copy appears here. So, you can see here that
my insurance is from
Bajaj Company.
This is the insurance of Bajaj Company and this
insurance of mine is not on the net. Your
insurance may also be from Bajaj,
HDFC, ICC and
many other banks.  It can be of all those banks
or of any company like Tata
or any other company, if you have
insurance of any company, your insurance is
not showing on the net, then what do you have to do,
first of all you
can see the insurance, this is the insurance,
this insurance has been around for
two-three months but till now it is
not showing on the net, so
you can see here, this is the
insurance here, so first of all I
back up here, after backing up you have to search the
name of your company, whatever your company is, like your insurance is of ICC Bank HDFC company, you have to open Google in your phone and search,
as it is done here,
we type Bajaj here, you can see it,
I have typed Bajaj here,
after typing Bajaj, you will
get the Bajaj Insurance email ID here, you have to simply
click on it, if
you click on it,
you will see Bajaj here
and here you will see the contact, simply
click on it,
as you click on it  So here
you will see an interface like this
Customer Service
Connect with
Service Related Issues, here you will
get the numbers of BSNL
Bharti and others and here you will get an email ID, you
can see here that you have got the email ID as
well, so you simply have to
copy this email ID here, you have to make the email ID,
after copying the email ID you have to go back
here, after going back you will get
Gmail here, you can see it here,
you have to click on Gmail, as if
you click on Gmail, an
interface like this will open in front of you,
you have to click on compose
here, you can see it on compose,
you have to simply click on it, as if you
click on compose, your
email ID will be shown here,
whichever is your email ID
from which you want to send the mail, so here
we have to select the email ID here
and here you will get the
email ID of the company, that is, whatever company's insurance you have, you will get the email ID of the company.  You have to
enter it here,
after entering the email ID you have to click on add,
as if you will click on add then the
email ID will start
showing here like this, so what you have to
write here in the subject, in the subject you have to
write
insurance note
update online, you can see here,
I have typed it here
insurance note update online
my insurance
policy,
but
my insurance
here, you can see, you
can see the insurance here, that is my insurance is
done but
my insurance is not showing on the net, it
is not showing online, you have to
type it something like this, you can
see here dear sir my insurance policy isood but
insurance note is showing, so here
you have to type it like this, that is the
number of your car,
bike, truck, tractor,
whatever is your number of the car,
you have to enter the same number here
and whatever is your number here,
you have to enter that number, whatever is the
car number of your bike,
after entering it here you have to enter a number  The
option of attack will show here, you can see
attack, you have to click on it, on the attack file,
as you will click on it, the
attack file which you will see here, after clicking on it, an
interface like this will appear in front of you, it is showing here,
my insurance is showing here
and here the PAN card is showing here,
RC here, so here you will have to upload your
insurance, your PAN card and your
RC in it,
after selecting here you simply have to
click on select and here
your PAN card, RC etc. will start
showing here like this, so
friend, here you have to
type the message like this, after typing the message
you have to click on send here,
as if you will click on send, then
this mail which is here has been sent here,
friend,
your mail which has been sent here will be sent here,
so friend your policy will start showing on the net,
how much time will it take for you,
one to two days  Or within two to three days
your insurance policy will start
showing on the net very easily,
your insurance will start showing on the net,
you just have to follow this process, you can
see your insurance on the net
very easily and you
can also back out after getting your challan,
friend, see you in the next video.